http://www.ringedhook.com/privacy-policy/

Loading... Please wait...
My Account
Order Status
View Cart
Sign in or Create an account
CONNECT WITH US:
Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting RingedHooks.com. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using this site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.
Collection of Information We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our customers. The information you provide is used to fulfill your order. This information is only used to fulfill your specific order.
Distribution of Information We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.
Commitment to Data Security Your personally identifiable information is kept secure, we do not sell your information.
Privacy Contact Information If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below: By e-mail: Guy@RingedHooks.com By Phone: 714-745-1269
We reserve the right to make changes to this policy and changes to our website. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
CONNECT WITH US:
© 2012 COPYRIGHT
RINGEDHOOKS.COM
Happy Fishing
